Finding Aid for Frank Murphy Papers, 1908-1949
Bentley Historical Library
- Speech File, 1908-1947
  - Message to the 59th Michigan Legislature, January 7, 1937 (Reel 142)
  - National Conference for Clarifying the Constitution by Amendment, February 1, 1937 (Reel 142)
  - American Irish Historical Society, New York City, February 13, 1937 (Reel 142)
  - Spring Rally of the Detroit District Holy Name Society, March 21, 1937 (Reel 142)
  - WJR Radio Address on behalf of Democratic candidates, Detroit Spring Election, March 28, 1937 (Reel 142)
  - Jefferson Club Testimonial Banquet for Murray D. Van Wagoner, State Highway Commissioner, March 29, 1937 (Reel 142)
  - Patriot's Day Banquet, Massachusetts State Council of Knights of Columbus, Boston, April 18, 1937 (Reel 142)
  - Annual Conference of the Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, Washington, D.C., May 1, 1937 (Reel 142)
  - Annual Luncheon of the Consumer's League of New York, New York City, May 14, 1937 (Reel 142)
  - National Conference of Social Work, Indianapolis, Indiana, May 28, 1937 (Reel 143)
  - Commencement Exercises, University of Detroit, June 8, 1937 (Reel 143)
  - Commencement Exercises, Duquesne University, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, June 9, 1937 (Reel 143)
  - Pamphlet: "Selected Addresses of Hon. Frank Murphy, Governor of Michigan, January 1 to, June 30, 1937 (Reel 143)
  - Governor's Dinner, Democratic Gathering, Mackinac Is, July 10, 1937 (Reel 143)
  - "The Shaping of a Labor Policy", Survey Graphic, July 23, 1937 (Reel 143)
  - Message to the Legislature, July 29, 1937 (Reel 143)
  - Greeting to the Most Rev. Edward A. Mooney, Archbishop-Elect of the Diocese of Detroit, August 3, 1937 (Reel 143)
  - Democratic Women's Study Clubs of California, Long Beach, August 17, 1937 (Reel 143)
  - CBS Radio Address, "Can Violence be Kept Out of Industrial Conflict?", September 24, 1937 (Reel 143)
  - State Convention of Young Democrats, Muskegon, Michigan, October 16, 1937 (Reel 143)
  - Notes for address to the University Press Club, Ann Arbor, Michigan, November 4, 1937 (Reel 143)
  - "Industrial Peace", The Christian Front, November 1937 (Reel 143)
  - December2 "The Shape of Things to Come", 25th Anniversary Dinner of Survey Associates, New York City, 1937 (Reel 143)
  - "Democracy and Religious Freedom", Fiftieth Anniversary Celebration of Yeshiva College, New York City, December 11, 1937 (Reel 143)
  - Articles, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Messages and press releases, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Miscellaneous speeches, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - "Michigan's Agriculture", Farmers' Week, Michigan State College, February 3, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Radio Address, Station WBEO, Marquette, Michigan, February 21, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Notes for Radio Address delivered at a public dinner, Hancock, Michigan, February 22, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - "Labor's New Day", Detroit and Wayne County Federation of Labor, Detroit, Michigan, March 8, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - "Irish-Americans and the New Fight for Freedom", Irish-American Association, Lackawanna County, Scranton, Pennsylvania, March 17, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Annual Banquet, Jeffersonian Club, Wichita, Kansas, April 13, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Jefferson Day Banquet, Saginaw, Michigan, April 20, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Radio Address on the President's Recovery Program, April 22, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Dedication of an addition to the Ypsilanti State Hospital, April 29, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Democratic Rally, Kalamazoo, Michigan, May 4, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Annual Convention of Michigan Congress of Parents and Teachers, Battle Creek, Michigan, May 5, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Radio Address on behalf of the Van Antwerp Library, Station WXYZ, Detroit, Michigan, May 6, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Dedication of Rural Electrification Cooperative, Ontonagon, Michigan, May 8, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - "A Profession of Faith", Democratic Spring Frolic, Detroit, Michigan, May 13, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - "Music and American Youth", remarks on a Broadcast of the Music Educators' National Conference, Station WWJ, Detroit, Michigan, May 15, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Remarks on the Detroit News and Detroit Board of Education Broadcast, Stations WWJ and W8XWJ, Detroit, Michigan, May 23, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Commencement Exercises of St. John's University, Brooklyn, New York, June 7, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Commencement Exercises, Michigan State College, East Lansing, Michigan, June 13, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Notes for Address at Dedication of Rural Electrification Project, Ubly, Michigan, June 18, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Notes for address at Dedication of the Grand Rapids Office of the Michigan State Employment Service, June 28, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Remarks Introducing Chairman Frank Picard on an Unemployment Compensation Broadcast, Station WXYZ, Detroit, Michigan, June 30, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Address on Radio Broadcast marking the Inauguration, July 1, of the Michigan Unemployment Compensation Program, Station WJR, Detroit, Michigan, June 30, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Recovery Rainbow Address (Nationwide Broadcast), Station WJR, Detroit, Michigan, July 9, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Notes for address at Traverse City, Michigan, July 15, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Dedication of the Fruit Belt Electric Cooperative, Cassopolis, Michigan, July 30, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Radio Address commemorating writing of first Michigan Unemployment Compensation check, Stations WJR and WXYZ, Detroit, Michigan, August 1, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Annual Rally of the Farmers' Educational and Cooperative Union, Western Michigan Branch, Grandville, Michigan, August 6, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Ceremonies held in memory of Father Marquette, Ludington, Michigan, August 7, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Message to the Special Session of the Legislature, Lansing, Michigan, August 29, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Dedication of Tri-County Electric Cooperative, Portland, Michigan, September 3, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Labor Day Address, Detroit, Michigan, September 5, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Ground-breaking ceremonies for addition to Michigan Children's Village, Coldwater, Michigan, September 9, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - State-wide Conference on Health, East Lansing, Michigan, September 10, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Notes for address at Annual Convention of Michigan Young Democrats, Bay City, Michigan, September 23, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Pamphlet "Selected Addresses of Frank Murphy, Governor of Michigan to September 30, 1938", January 1, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Democratic State Convention, Grand Rapids, Michigan, October 1, 1938 (Reel 143)
  - Dedication of Blue Water Bridge, Port Huron, Michigan, October 8, 1938 (Reel 144)
  - National Conference of Catholic Charities, Richmond, Virginia, October 9, 1938 (Reel 144)
  - Notes for address at Mt. Clemens, Michigan, Businessmen's Luncheon, October 11, 1938 (Reel 144)
  - Press release on address at Pontiac, Michigan, October 12, 1938 (Reel 144)
  - Notes for meeting of Commission on Reform and Modernization of Government, October 13, 1938 (Reel 144)
  - Press release on address at Bay City, Michigan. Subject: Milk Study Commission, October 13, 1938 (Reel 144)
  - Press release on address at Saginaw, Michigan, October 14, 1938 (Reel 144)
  - Press release on address at Menominee, Michigan. Subject: Securities Commission, October 15, 1938 (Reel 144)
  - Press release on address at Marquette, Michigan, October 16, 1938 (Reel 144)
  - Press release on address at Muskegon, Michigan, October 16, 1938 (Reel 144)
  - Civil Service address prepared for delivery at Lansing, Michigan (not given), October 20, 1938 (Reel 144)
  - October 21, 1938
    - Sit-Down Strikes, Flint, Michigan, I.M.A. Auditorium (Reel 144)
    - Press release on address at Lapeer, Michigan (Reel 144)
    - Fall Frolic of the Unemployment Compensation Commission, Detroit, Michigan (Reel 144)
  - Station WJR, Detroit, Michigan, radio address, October 22, 1938 (Reel 144)
  - Radio address on the Dies Committee Sit-Down Strike Hearings, Jackson, Michigan, October 24, 1938 (Reel 144)
  - Press release on address at Kalamazoo, Michigan. Subject: Chrysler Strike, October 25, 1938 (Reel 144)
  - Radio address on Health Program, Battle Creek, Michigan, October 26, 1938 (Reel 144)
  - Press releases (2) on address at Benton Harbor, Michigan, October 27, 1938 (Reel 144)
  - Press release on address at Grand Rapids, Michigan. Subject: Relief, October 28, 1938 (Reel 144)
  - Radio address on Relief and the "Communism Issue". Station WJR, Detroit, Michigan, October 29, 1938 (Reel 144)
  - Radio address on "Democracy". Station WJR, Detroit, Michigan, October 30, 1938 (Reel 144)
  - October 31, 1938
    - Radio address on Mortgage Moratorium and Deficiency Judgments. Station WXYZ, Detroit, Michigan (Reel 144)
    - Notes for address at Monroe, Michigan (Reel 144)
  - Radio address on Education. Station WJR, Detroit, Michigan, November 1, 1938 (Reel 144)
  - November 2, 1938
    - Radio address on the "Communism Issue". Station WXYZ, Detroit, Michigan (Reel 144)
    - Remarks introducing Hon. Nathan Straus at the Dedication of Brewster Housing Project. Station NBC, Detroit, Michigan (Reel 144)
  - Radio address on State Finances. Station WJR, Detroit, Michigan, November 3, 1938 (Reel 144)
  - Radio address on Labor Relations and Economic Recovery. Station WXYZ, Detroit, Michigan, November 4, 1938 (Reel 144)
  - Radio address on Women and Government. Station WXYZ, Detroit, Michigan, November 5, 1938 (Reel 144)
  - November 6, 1938
    - Address prepared for Radio Broadcast from Port Huron, Michigan (Reel 144)
    - Radio address on Progress. Station WJR, Detroit, Michigan (Reel 144)
  - Final Campaign Address, Statewide Broadcast. Stations WXYZ, WJR, WWJ, Detroit, Michigan, November 7, 1938 (Reel 144)
  - Suggested radio address dealing with the welfare reorganization laws subject to referendum vote on November 8 (Act 257, P.A. 1937), November 8, 1938 (Reel 144)
  - Miscellaneous speeches, press releases, and articles, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - Ex-Augural Message to Michigan Legislature, January 5, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - Jackson Day Banquet, Detroit, Michigan, January 6, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - Statement of Honorable Frank Murphy, Attorney General of the United States, before a Sub-Committee of the Committee on the Judiciary of the United States Senate, January 13, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - Department of Justice press release, February 3, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - Notes for speech at National Press Club, Washington, D.C., March 14, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - March 17, 1939
    - The Hibernian Society of Baltimore, Maryland (Reel 144)
    - Memorial broadcast for Governor Frank Fitzgerald, Detroit, Michigan (Reel 144)
  - Notes on University of Michigan broadcast, March 18, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - Memorial broadcast for Gov. Frank Fitzgerald, March 19, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - "Civil Liberties" National Radio Forum. Station NBC, Washington, D.C., March 27, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - Graduation class of National Police Academy, FBI, Department of Justice, April 1, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - Jefferson Day Dinner, Philadelphia, Pa. "The Democratic Crisis in America", April 13, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - April 17, 1939
    - Introduction of President Roosevelt to National Parole Conference (Reel 144)
    - Keynote address, National Parole Conference, Washington D.C. (Reel 144)
  - Keynote address at Conference of U.S. Attorneys, April 19, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - Closing remarks at Conference of U.S. Attorneys, April 21, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - "The Federal Courts" delivered at annual luncheon of the Associated Press, New York, April 24, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - Fourth in series of Interviews with Cabinet Members by Lowell Mellett. Station NBC (broadcast June 6, 1939), May 3, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - "Civil Liberties and the Cities", U.S. Conference of Mayors, May 15, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - "The Substance of Freedom", New Mexico State College, May 23, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - "The Evolution of a Century", Louisiana State University, May 29, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - "The Lawyer and the Economy of Tomorrow", Georgetown University, June 1, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - June 2, 1939 Statement before the Senate Committee on Education and Labor. Subject: Lafollette-Thomas S., 1970 the Oppressive Labor Practices Act, 1939-1970 (Reel 144)
  - "Youth in the World of Tomorrow", YMCA International Fire of Friendship Ceremony, New York World's Fair, June 6, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - "The Return of Religion", St. Joseph's College Commencement, Philadelphia, June 13, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - "The Right Use of Democracy", National Catholic Social Action Conference, Cleve, June 14, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - "Better Servants for Democracy", broadcast to Civil Service Assembly, June 15, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - Memorial Services for Senator Robert M. Lafollette, Sr., Madison, Wisconsin, June 18, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - "The Meaning of Civil Liberty", John Marshall College, Jersey City, New Jersey, June 21, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - September 25, 1939
    - "Our Heritage of Justice", 150th Anniversary of the Department of Justice, Washington D.C. (Reel 144)
    - Meeting of Motion Picture Award, Democratic Committee, Hollywood, California (address not given) (Reel 144)
  - Conference of Senior Circuit Judges, September 28, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - Graduation class of National Police Academy, FBI, Department of Justice, September 30, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - Tribute to George Cardinal Mundelein, NBC program, Washington D.C., October 3, 1939 (Reel 144)
  - "The Test of Patriotism", National Conference on Civil Liberties, New York City, October 13, 1939 (Reel 145)
  - "Keeper of the Faith", Ten Year Achievement Dinner in honor of Dr. Alexander G. Ruthven, Ann Arbor, Michigan, October 27, 1939 (Reel 145)
  - Community Chest Campaign Luncheon, Willard Hotel, Washington D.C., November 13, 1939 (Reel 145)
  - Articles and press releases, 1940 (Reel 145)
  - "The Challenge of Intolerance", National Conference for Palestine, Washington D.C., January 7, 1940 (Reel 145)
  - "The Higher Duty", Carroll Club Twentieth Annual Corporate Communion Breakfast, New York City, January 14, 1940 (Reel 145)
  - 104th Anniversary, New York University School of Law. Annual dinner of the Alumni Association, March 2, 1940 (Reel 145)
  - Radio talk on behalf of the U.S. Committee for the Care of European Children, July 5, 1940 (Reel 145)
  - Articles and miscellaneous messages, 1941 (Reel 145)
  - Report of President's Committee on Civil Service Improvement, February 1941 (Reel 145)
  - "Foundations of Freedom", Commencement Exercises, Tulane University, New Orleans, June 11, 1941 (Reel 145)
  - Tribute Broadcast to Chief Justice Charles E. Hughes, June 30, 1941 (Reel 145)
  - "Nazi Revolution and Religious Freedom". Convention of Knights of Columbus, Atlantic City, New Jersey, August 19, 1941 (Reel 145)
  - The American Committee for British Catholic Relief, Inc., December 22, 1941 (Reel 145)
  - Message to the people of the Philippine Islands, December 30, 1941 (Reel 145)
  - St. Louis Bar Association, January 23, 1942 (Reel 145)
  - Inter-Racial War Bond Rally. Olympia Stadium, Detroit, May 31, 1942 (Reel 145)
  - Commencement Exercises, Creighton University, Omaha, Nebraska, June 4, 1942 (Reel 145)
  - Radio address, station WBT, Charlotte, North Carolina, July 27, 1942 (Reel 145)
  - March of Time, New York broadcast, October 1, 1942 (Reel 145)
  - Army Hour broadcast, Washington D.C., October 25, 1942 (Reel 145)
  - Advertising Club of Boston, November 5, 1942 (Reel 145)
  - Miscellaneous articles and speeches, 1943 (Reel 145)
  - Radio broadcast in commemoration of the 8th anniversary of the establishment of the Philippine Commonwealth, November 15, 1943 (Reel 145)
  - Miscellaneous articles and speeches, 1944 (Reel 145)
  - "Anti-Semitism is an Un-American and Un-Christian Practice", B'Nai B'Rith Convention, Carnegie Hall, New York, May 8, 1944 (Reel 145)
  - "The American Way of Life-Can It Survive?", Civic Auditorium, San Francisco, Cal., September 10, 1944 (Reel 145)
  - Miscellaneous articles and speeches, 1945 (Reel 145)
  - "Interdependence for Americans", Hollywood Bowl, Hollywood, California, July 4, 1945 (Reel 145)
  - Commencement Exercises, Bennington College, Bennington, Vermont, July 20, 1945 (Reel 145)
  - Miscellaneous articles and speeches, 1946 (Reel 146)
  - Hunter College, New York City, April 12, 1946 (Reel 146)
  - Miscellaneous articles and speeches, 1947 (Reel 146)
- Speech Material
  Speech Material (Rolls 146-147, Boxes 77-83). The designation "speech material" was one used by Frank Murphy and his secretary, Eleanor Bumgardner, and is not wholly descriptive of the types of materials in this series. Though consisting largely of pamphlets, magazine articles, and newspaper clippings, the files also contain reports, memoranda, and campaign miscellanea. While these materials may have been used as background resources for future speeches, they also seem to have served as a topical file for Murphy and his staff. In preparing this series for microfilming,the processing staff divided it into two parallel files, one (in Box 77, Rolls 146-147) which relates specifically to Frank Murphy, and the other (in Boxes 78-83, not microfilmed) which contains materials of a more general nature.
  - Information about Frank Murphy
    - A [Miscellaneous] (Reel 146)
    - Agriculture (Reel 146)
    - B-P [Misc.] (Reel 146)
    - Politics (Michigan and National)
      - Newspaper Clippings (Michigan) (Reel 146)
      - Murphy campaign, 1936 (Reel 146)
      - Campaign issues, 1936 (Reel 146)
      - Platform and policy, Democratic National Convention, 1936 (Reel 146)
      - Campaign schedules, circa 1936 (Reel 146)
      - Michigan election returns, 1936; 1938 (Reel 146)
      - Campaign speeches (supporting Murphy), 1936 (Reel 146)
      - Campaign materials, 1938 (Reel 146)
      - Campaign leaflets, 1938 (Reel 146)
      - Political speeches (supporting Murphy), 1938 (Reel 146)
      - Campaign issues, 1938
        - Old age assistance (Reel 146)
        - Welfare (Reel 147)
      - Clippings re State politics, 1938-1942 (Reel 147)
    - R-U [Misc.] (Reel 147)
  - Non-Murphy
    - A [Misc.] (Box 78)
    - Agriculture (Box 78)
    - Americanism (Box 78)
    - Anti-Trust (Box 78)
    - B [Misc.] (Box 78)
    - Banks and banking (Box 78)
    - Birth control (Box 78)
    - Budget (Box 78)
    - Business (Box 78)
    - C [Misc.] (Box 78)
    - Campaigns-see Politics (Box 78)
    - Capital punishment (Box 78)
    - Capitolism (Box 78)
    - Catholics and the Catholic Church (Box 78)
    - China (Box 78)
    - Civil liberties (Box 78)
    - Civil service (Box 78)
    - Communism (Box 78)
    - Constitution (Box 78)
    - Correctional activities (probation, probation parole systems) (Box 78)
    - Coughlin, Charles E. (Box 79)
    - Crime (Box 79)
    - D [Misc.] (Box 79)
    - Democracy (Box 79)
    - Depression (Box 79)
    - Dies Committee (Box 79)
    - E [Misc.] (Box 79)
    - Economics (Box 79)
    - Education (Box 79)
    - F [Misc.] (Box 79)
    - Fascism (Box 79)
    - Finance (Box 79)
    - Foreign affairs (Box 79)
    - G [Misc.] (Box 79)
    - Germany (Box 79)
    - Government (Box 79)
    - H [Misc.] (Box 79)
    - Health and medicine (Box 79)
    - Highway (Box 79)
    - Holidays (Box 79)
    - Horses and polo (Box 79)
    - Housing (Box 79)
    - I [Misc.] (Box 79)
    - Industry (Box 79)
    - International subjects (Box 80)
    - Ireland (Box 80)
    - J [Misc.] (Box 80)
    - Japan (Box 80)
    - Judaism (Box 80)
    - Judiciary and judicial ethics (Box 80)
    - K [Misc.] (Box 80)
    - L [Misc.] (Box 80)
    - Labor and labor relations (Box 80)
    - Law and lawyers (Box 80)
    - Lincoln, Abraham (Box 80)
    - Lippmann, Walter (Box 80)
    - Liquor Commission (Box 80)
    - M [Misc.] (Box 80)
    - Men and women (Box 81)
    - Mental health (Box 81)
    - Mexico (Box 81)
    - Michigan (Box 81)
    - N [Misc.] (Box 81)
    - Neutrality legislation (Box 81)
    - New Deal (Box 81)
    - O [Misc.] (Box 81)
    - P [Misc.] (Box 81)
    - Palestine (Box 81)
    - Parole (Box 81)
    - Peace (Box 81)
    - Pensions (Box 81)
    - Philippine Islands (Box 81)
    - Politics (Michigan and national)
      - Newspaper clippings (Michigan) (Box 81)
      - Campaign issues, 1936 (Box 81)
      - Campaign schedules, circa 1936 (Box 81)
      - Speeches, Democratic National Convention, 1936 (Box 81)
      - Platform and policy, Democratic (Box 81)
      - National Convention, 1936 (Box 81)
    - Michigan delegates, Democratic National Convention, 1936 (Box 81)
    - Michigan election returns, 1936 (Box 81)
    - Campaign leaflets, 1936 (Box 81)
    - Campaign literature, 1936 (Box 81)
    - Suggested Michigan topics for Democratic speakers, 1936 (Box 81)
    - Clippings concerning Presidential campaign, 1936 (Box 81)
    - Miscellanea, 1936 (Box 81)
    - Political speeches (non-Murphy), 1937 (Box 81)
    - Primary and general election statistics, 1938 (Box 81)
      - Campaign materials, 1938 (Box 82)
      - Campaign leaflets, 1938 (Box 82)
      - Political speeches (non-Murphy), 1938 (Box 82)
      - Campaign issues, 1938
        - Old Age Assistance (Box 82)
        - Welfare (Box 82)
        - Payroll Boosts (Box 82)
      - Michigan State Federation of Democratic Women's Clubs, Democratic Women of Wayne, Speakers' Bureau miscellanea, 1938 (Box 82)
      - Clippings concerning state politics, 1938 (Box 82)
      - Articles and newsletters concerning Michigan politics, 1940 (Box 82)
      - Election statistics, 1940-1942 (Box 82)
      - Clippings concerning state politics, 1940 (Box 82)
      - Political speeches (non-Murphy), 1939-1940 (Box 82)
      - Clippings concerning national politics, 1940 (Box 82)
      - Campaign materials (national), 1940 (Box 82)
      - Articles concerning national campaign, 1940 (Box 82)
      - Papers concerning national politics, 1941 (Box 82)
      - Miscellanea (Box 82)
    - Prose quotations (Box 82)
    - R [miscellaneous] (Box 82)
    - Railroads (Box 82)
    - Recovery (Box 82)
    - Relief (Box 82)
    - Religion (Box 82)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano
      - Campaign miscellanea (Box 83)
      - Biographical miscellanea (Box 83)
      - Newspaper clippings (Box 83)
    - S [miscellaneous] (Box 83)
    - Science (Box 83)
    - Social justice (Box 83)
    - Spain (Box 83)
    - Suffrage (Philippine Islands) (Box 83)
    - Supreme Court Reorganization Plan (Box 83)
    - T [miscellaneous] (Box 83)
    - Taxation (Box 83)
    - U [miscellaneous] (Box 83)
    - Unemployment (Box 83)
    - Unemployment Compensation and Insurance (Box 83)
    - V [miscellaneous] (Box 83)
    - W [miscellaneous] (Box 83)
    - Wages (Box 83)
    - Wage and Hour Law (Box 83)
    - Wagner Act (Box 83)
    - War (general) (Box 83)
    - World War II (Box 83)
- Miscellaneous
  Miscellaneous Material (Rolls 147-154, Boxes 84-94, 100-104). This series includes invitations, personal (mostly romantic) correspondence, F.B.I. files, printed works, and other miscellaneous materials. Of these, the personal correspondence (Box 86) and the appointment calendars (Box 90) were microfilmed. The remaining categories: material documenting Murphy's personal finances, miscellaneous lists, etc. (Box 84); invitations (Box 85); the F.B.I. records from 1939 when Frank Murphy was Attorney General, which are closed until January 1, 2015 (Boxes 87-89); and printed materials (Boxes 91-94) were not included in the microfilm project.
  - Personal correspondence (largely of a romantic nature) (Reel 147)
    - Undated (Reel 147)
    - 1919-1929 (Reel 147)
    - 1920s undated (Reel 147)
    - 1930-1937 (Reel 148)
    - 1938-1949, 1940s undated (Reel 149)
  - Book lists and notes on books, circa 1932-1949 (Box 84)
  - Christmas card, gift, and other lists (Box 84)
  - Medical receipts and miscellanea, 1933-1949 (Box 84)
    [Restricted access]
  - Autograph book (Box 84)
  - Membership cards (Box 84)
  - Business and announcement cards (Box 84)
  - Receipts and other financial material (Box 84)